[
    {
        "category": "Computer Science",
        "QuestionAnswer": [
            {
                "Question": "This is the art of teaching a computer what to do",
                "Value": "200",
                "Answer": "What is Computer Science?",
                "ID": 1
            },
            {
                "Question": "[Blank] started out as basic calculators",
                "Value": "400",
                "Answer": "What are computers?",
                "ID": 2
            },
            {
                "Question": "Its just a language that you use to talk to the computer.",
                "Value": "800",
                "Answer": "What is a programming language?",
                "ID": 3
            },
            {
                "Question": "Becoming a [blank] is one of the best ways to have an impact on the world because you can influence so many peoples lives with the things you make.",
                "Value": "1200",
                "Answer": "What is a Programmer?",
                "ID": 4
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Computers",
        "QuestionAnswer": [
            {
                "Question": "A computer monitor is an example of [blank].",
                "Value": "200",
                "Answer": "What are outputs?",
                "ID": 5
            },
            {
                "Question": "Keyboards is an example of [blank].",
                "Value": "400",
                "Answer": "What are inputs ?",
                "ID": 6
            },
            {
                "Question": "Information captured from inputs, are stored into [blank].",
                "Value": "800",
                "Answer": "What is memory?",
                "ID": 7
            },
            {
                "Question": "[Blank] are machines that take in input and give output.",
                "Value": "1200",
                "Answer": "What are computers?",
                "ID": 8
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Binary and Data",
        "QuestionAnswer": [
            {
                "Question": "Computers work on [blank] and [blank].",
                "Value": "200",
                "Answer": "What are 1s and 0s?",
                "ID": 9
            },
            {
                "Question": "This on/off state of a single wire is called a [blank].",
                "Value": "400",
                "Answer": "What is a bit?",
                "ID": 10
            },
            {
                "Question": "Inside a computer are electric [blank] and [blank] that carry all the information in a computer.",
                "Value": "800",
                "Answer": "What are wires and circuits?",
                "ID": 11
            },
            {
                "Question": "An image is made out of teeny dots called [blank].",
                "Value": "1200",
                "Answer": "What are pixels?",
                "ID": 12
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Hardware and Software",
        "QuestionAnswer": [
            {
                "Question": "Circuits and Chips are considered [blank] while Xbox and PlayStation games are considered [blank].",
                "Value": "200",
                "Answer": "What is hardware and software?",
                "ID": 13
            },
            {
                "Question": "The [Blank] is a program with special abilities that control the other software on the computer .",
                "Value": "400",
                "Answer": "What is the operating system?",
                "ID": 14
            },
            {
                "Question": "[Blank] is the master chip that controls all the other parts of the computer.",
                "Value": "800",
                "Answer": "What is the CPU?",
                "ID": 15
            },
            {
                "Question": "[Blank] is the most basic form of software and it controls all the hardware of a computer.",
                "Value": "1200",
                "Answer": "What is binary code?",
                "ID": 16
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Programming",
        "QuestionAnswer": [
            {
                "Question": "Programming languages fall into 2 different groups [Blank] and [Blank].",
                "Value": "200",
                "Answer": "What are low level and high level languages?",
                "ID": 17
            },
            {
                "Question": "Programming languages that are close to machine code are considered a [blank] language.",
                "Value": "400",
                "Answer": "What is a low level?",
                "ID": 18
            },
            {
                "Question": "Python is an example of a [blank] language.",
                "Value": "800",
                "Answer": "What is a high level?",
                "ID": 19
            },
            {
                "Question": "A series of commands.",
                "Value": "1200",
                "Answer": "What is an algorithm?",
                "ID": 20
            }
        ]
    }
]